

ZUKISA ERIC MAZA

Software Developer & CyberSecurity

About Me

First and Foremost, I love writing code. Ever since writing my first program in Python and manipulating it to produce a desired output, I have been obsessed with the idea of using software to solve practical problems.

I am passionate about developing complex applications that solve real-world problems impacting millions of users.

- 0723484826 || 0699950266
- maza2pac77@gmail.com
- 4711 Ruth first str,
 Weltevreden North,
 Mitchel's Plain, 7785

Language

- English
- IsiXhosa (expert)
- IsiZulu (basic)

Expertise

- Management Skills
- Creativity
- Life Skills
- Professionalism
- Critical Thinking
- Leadership
- Data Visualization
- Problem Solver

Hobbies

- Chess
 - Soccer
- Checkers Draught Puzzle

Experience

Umuzi Photo Club

Johannesburg - Gauteng

2019 - 2021

Worked on three web applications targeting customers, selling vendors, and admin users; built 50+ RESTful APIs with functionalities such as login/sign up, view a product, add a product to cart.

Robertson & Caine

Century City - Western Cape

2022 - 2023

As a storeman at Robertson and Caine's electricity store for cruises, I am responsible for managing inventory, ensuring efficient operations, and providing exceptional customer service to meet the unique needs of our clients in the maritime industry.

UCT/GSB Solution Space

Phillipi Village - Western Cape

2023 - 2023

Devised a customized recursion algorithm to extend the functionality of the current environment to a multi-robot and multi-system environment.

Life Choices Academy

Claremont - Western Cape

2023 - Present

Delivered a solution for a POC involving Automatic Financial Document Classifier using Natural Language Processing and Support Vector.

Education

Umuzi Academy

Information Technology System Development 2019 - 2020

Sophumelela Secondary School

Matric Certificate

2013 - 2017

Skills Summary

Design Process Project Management

JavaScript Python HTML5 & CSS3 Diango **Express** TyperScript Angular React Vue MySQL Moongose Node MongoDB Pytorch Git/GitHub/GitLab C++